Oh my gosh.
Where's that last one?
Wow, my heart is actually racing.
Wow.
All right, I got to take a picture of
this.
You know, my friends asked me if I was
going to cry when I hit it. I was like,
"No, of course not."
No, all jokes aside, this is just a
really special day for me. I've got this
filter right here set up to be September
19th, 2024, all the way until today,
which is just under 2 years. This is
obviously a huge milestone, and it's a
very surreal moment for me because, man,
the past 2 years have gone so, so fast.
I've learned so much. I've had so much
fun. I've also been very stressed out,
but it's just been a crazy 2 years. Oh
my gosh, look at this.
My heart rate right now?
93. My resting, it says, is normally
like 54, but
>> [laughter]
>> Wow, I mean, that really hits you. Wow.
Seeing that 1M right there looks great,
but man, if we come down here to the
videos and we go to the oldest,
look at look at young Nate. Young Nate
in here. If I click on this first one,
>> So, AI agents, there's so much
information out there. It can be
overwhelming trying to learn about them.
So, I wanted to come in here and break
it down simply, just the way that I wish
someone would have explained it to me.
>> Oh my gosh, he's got a lot to learn
about them, this young guy. But man, it
is September 19th, 2024. So, about 6
months before I made this video, I
graduated from the University of Iowa,
and I moved out to Salt Lake City.
And I was starting my full-time role
with Goldman Sachs, and I was automating
stuff. And I started to fall in love
with the process of making videos and
and educating. And it took me a while
from when I started basically making
money with AI to being able to, I guess,
sort of work up the courage and also,
you know, get my parents on board with
letting me, you know, quit this stable
job and and, you know,
go out on my own and try to build
something. And obviously, I'm just so
glad I took that leap and I cannot thank
my parents enough for, you know, always
supporting what I want to do. My
friends, my family, you know, everybody
in my ecosystem, my whole support
system,
I cannot thank all of you guys enough.
My team at, you know, Up At AI, what
we're building here with AI Automation
Society, we are almost at half a million
members here in the free group, and this
has just been the most rewarding thing
that I've ever done. Like it's truly, I
know it's cheesy, but this has truly
been a dream come true to be able to
wake up every day and be so excited to
come sit or stand here in front of you
guys and play around with tools and try
to show you what I'm learning. I truly
do wake up every day just feeling very
fortunate for
what I get to, you know, call my job.
And I could not have done any of this
without my team. John, I've got a huge
thank you to you for being such a great
mentor to me, for being the first person
that I brought on the team,
for teaching me so much and for helping
me understand who I want to be and how
we want to shape, you know, the brand of
AI Automation Society. A lot of you guys
in the communities ask me
how I'm able to make so many videos and
yes, I have AI agents that help me with,
you know, looking through comments and
ideation and packaging and all of these
things now, but the answer is it's John.
It's John and the team. There's no way I
could be putting out the, you know,
amount of videos that I put out if it
wasn't for the team. And that's not
something that any AI agents or
automations will ever be able to replace
or should ever replace. Huge shoutout to
Yash, our community manager. He has been
around watching my channel since I was
at like 8,000 subscribers, I think he
said. And before we brought him on, he
was
actively participating and engaging in
the community. Just
an amazing person. Every single person
on the Up At AI team, I love you guys.
Thank you so much for everything you
guys do. And to all you guys, you know,
obviously, it goes without saying none
of this could happen without all of you
guys. The supportive comments, the ones
that are a little bit sarcastic, um all
of them, you know, they they fire me up
and they they make me want to do more.
And for all the times that you guys have
had to put up with me saying costed
instead of saying cost,
thank you for your patience. I remember
making every single one of these
thumbnails. I remember editing every
single one of these videos. I remember
not even having a microphone for so long
and just using the little, you know, $30
webcam that I had right here. I remember
you guys saying in the comments, "Please
get a microphone. Please get a better
webcam." I remember I kept this towel on
my desk so I could put it under my
keyboard so that when I would type in
videos, it didn't just like bang bang
bang bang the microphone. When you guys
in the community, whether it's AIS or
it's AS Plus or it's a certification
program or our events or whatever it is,
when you guys tell me that I was able to
contribute a little bit into something
you built or into you closing a client
or signing a big deal or getting a crazy
job opportunity or anything like that,
those things just make my day. I have
just met so many cool people through,
you know, making content. So many cool
people from the communities that I've
gotten to meet in person. So many cool
people that I've gotten to meet in these
Q&As or at these live events. And so
many other cool content creators in the
space that are making AI content or
business content or whatever it may be.
It's just been a really incredible 2
years. I am, you know, very happy right
now, feeling very blessed. And I'm
really excited because there's still so
much that I want to do. You know,
there's so many things that I want to
try. There's so many things that I want
AI Automation Society to achieve and
that I want Up At AI as a whole to do.
And I think the coolest part about this
is I have so much to learn. Every single
day I learn something new. Every single
month I learn something new. Every
conversation I have with someone else on
my team, I learn something from. I very
specifically remember losing this deal
when I had gone through maybe this was
the fourth or fifth call with this
potential client and they ended up not
going with us because they said that we
were too young and they didn't like the
fact that at this point I was only 23
years old. And I honestly understood.
Like I get that. But I think what's
really cool about life is that everyone
has a different experience and everyone
can teach someone something. And it's
really just about finding what is it
that you're passionate about and what is
it that you
know a lot about and how can you fill in
a gap that someone else might have.
Expertise is always relative and I I I
truthfully don't think that the imposter
syndrome ever goes away. It just depends
on the room you're in and the people
that you're around. So anyways, I'm
going to go ahead and stop yapping here.
I'm going to get back to work, but I'm
so so excited for everything that I
still
get to do and everything that I still
get to learn. And I'm so excited about
the people that I get to learn and build
and share things with. So So thank you
guys again so so much. Um seriously just
making my dreams come true and you know,
this was obviously a big milestone and
it's making me super happy today. So
that is going to do it for today. If you
guys enjoyed or you learned something
new, please give it a like. It helps me
out a ton. And as always, I appreciate
you making it to the end of the video
and I'll see you guys all in the next
one.
Thanks, everyone.